Guide to the North American Institute Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
North American Institute records
1987-2008
SC0926
North American Institute (Santa Fe, N.M.)
12.5 Linear feet
Collection primarily consists of correspondence, photographs, and conference materials. Includes audio and video recordings of speeches given at various conferences and events.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The North American Institute (NAMI) was founded by John D. Wirth in 1988 to enhance public understanding of priority issues affecting the North American community. NAMI is a private, not-for-profit tri-national organization with a secretariat in Santa Fe, New Mexico, and chapters in Canada and Mexico.
Description of the Collection
Collection primarily consists of correspondence, photographs, and conference materials. Includes audio and video recordings of speeches given at various conferences and events.
Access Terms
North American Institute (Santa Fe, N.M.); Wirth, John D.; Environmental policy--Canada.; Environmental policy--Mexico.; Environmental policy--United States.; Environmental protection--International cooperation.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - San Antonio Conference Correspondence, 6/6-6/7/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - San Antonio Conference Papers, 6/6-6/7/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board Meeting, 5/10/1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Meeting, 12/6/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agenda - San Antonio Executive Committee, 6/8/1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - San Antonio Conference Address List, 6/6-6/7/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - San Antonio Conference Agenda, 6/6-6/7/1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - San Antonio Conference Bios, 6/6-6/7/1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - San Antonio Conference Participants, 6/6-6/7/1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Plaza San Antonio Hotel - Promotional Material, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - La Mansion Hotel - Promotional Material, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Environmental Education and Training Institute of North America Board of Directors Meeting, 10/9/1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Transboundary Resource Inventory Project Conference, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - “North American Environmental Cooperation: Transition to Sustainable Development?” 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sanford Gaines Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fourth Quarter Commission for Environmental Cooperation Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NAMI, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Third Quarter Commission for Environmental Cooperation Correspondence, 1996 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Third Quarter Commission for Environmental Cooperation Correspondence, 1996 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Second Quarter Commission for Environmental Cooperation Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - First Quarter Commission for Environmental Cooperation Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Air Issue/CEC (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Werner Braun, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commission for Environmental Cooperation – Annual Program and Budget, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Multilateral Fund, “Working Together to Protect the Ozone Layer, “ (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Co-conveners Correspondence A-F, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Co-conveners Correspondence G-M, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Co-conveners Correspondence N-Z, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - February Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - San Diego Conference, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Border Attorneys General Conference, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Gamboa Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Form 990, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Executive Meeting, 1/26/1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NM Attorney General Filings, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NAMI-Notes by JDW, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - EETINA-Water, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - USP, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Educational Reform in Canada, Mexico, and the United States-Brown University, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Higher education reports, papers and preparation, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Approaches to the Problem of Mexican Identity by Ruy-Sanchez (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Social Welfare, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - NGO Forum (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - CEC 4th Quarter Correspondence, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CEC 3rd Quarter Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CEC 2nd Quarter Correspondence, 1997 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CEC 2nd Quarter Correspondence, 1997 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CEC 1st Quarter Correspondence, 1997 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CEC 1st Quarter Correspondence, 1997 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 10th Anniversary Forum-Santa Fe, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous-Website & Floppy Disks (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sharyn Udall-Correspondence re Kahlo, O’Keeffe, and Carr Exhibit, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - June/July Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - August/September Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - October/November/December Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CEC 1st Quarter Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CEC 1st Quarter, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CEC 3rd Quarter Correspondence, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CEC 2nd Quarter, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CEC 4th Quarter, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Articles, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - SME (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mexico: Culture and Identity in the Information Age (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - American Identity (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Citizenship and Civil Society-Ford Foundation Project Proposal, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Talking Points, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - January Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, March-May 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Genetic Engineering-Seeds (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, February-April 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, December 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - CEC 1st Quarter Correspondence, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - CEC 2nd Quarter Correspondence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - CEC 3rd Quarter Correspondence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - CEC 4th Quarter Correspondence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - North American Youth Conference, Carleton University, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, February-June 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, July-September 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Climate Change Forum, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hoover Library-NAMI, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Auto Industry Conference, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Speeches and Presentations, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - February Environmental Colloquium, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Senator Jack Austin-Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Rod Dobell-Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Emilio Carrillo G.-Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Dr. George Cowan-Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NAMI Country Core Groups, circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Identity, Culture and North American Society Conference, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Borders and Water: A Forum on North American Water Issues, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Wirth-Notes/Writings (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Conference/Lecture material, including speech text (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Conference/Lecture material, including speech text (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Background/Research material, 2001, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Public Service (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - San Diego Council on Foreign Relations – Agenda, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - San Diego Council on Foreign Relations – Participants, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - San Diego Council on Foreign Relations – Bios, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - San Diego Council on Foreign Relations – Address List, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - San Diego Council on Foreign Relations – Correspondence, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - San Diego Council on Foreign Relations – Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Social Policy Agenda, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Social Policy Address List, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Social Policy Participants List (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Social Policy Bios (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Social Policy Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Social Policy Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Media Hotel (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Media Agenda (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Media Participants List (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Media Address List (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Media Packet Originals (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Media Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Media Bios (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Media Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Preservation Agenda, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Preservation Hotel (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Preservation Registration (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Preservation Participants (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Federalism Agenda (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Federalism Address List (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Federalism Accounting (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Federalism Bios (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Federalism Packet Originals (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Federalism Participants List (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Federalism Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Federalism Papers (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Toronto Address List (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Toronto Agenda (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Toronto Participants (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Toronto Bios (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Toronto Conference Papers (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Toronto Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Toronto Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Texas A&M Press (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Business Roundtable (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Business Roundtable (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - California-Mexico Project at USC (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Los Caminos del Rio (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Canadian Environmental Law Association (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - US Candidates (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - US Participants – Potential (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - US Participants – Past (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - NAMI Bylaws (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - NAMI Founders Meeting Santa Fe, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of First NAMI ‘Convocation,’ December 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Initial Meeting, 1988 December 9-11 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - “Applying the Principles of Environmental Dispute Resolution to International Transboundary Conflicts,” 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pre-NAMI correspondence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Transcript of Conference, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, circa 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - NAMI Participants – Oaxtepec (1989), summaries (letters), Vancouver and San Francisco meeting, letters (1990), (1 of 4) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - NAMI Participants – Oaxtepec (1989), summaries (letters), Vancouver and San Francisco meeting, letters (1990), (2 of 4) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NAMI Participants – Oaxtepec (1989), summaries (letters), Vancouver and San Francisco meeting, letters (1990), (3 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - NAMI Participants – Oaxtepec (1989), summaries (letters), Vancouver and San Francisco meeting, letters (1990), (4 of 4) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1989 (1 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1989 (2 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - NAMI Correspondence, 1989 (3 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rancho Conference Transcript, 1989 June (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - NAMI 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - NAMI Energy & Environment Meeting – Oaxtepec, 1989 December (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Santa Fe Meeting Planning, 1989 June (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Victor Palmieri Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - NAMI General Correspondence, circa 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - NAMI General Correspondence, circa 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Articles of Incorporation, Bylaws, Certificates, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Conference Material, 1988-1991 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Conference Material, 1988-1991 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - NAMI – Background/Early Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - NAMI – Speeches (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Lectures/Presentations (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NAFTA Media Conference, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - North American Agreement on Environmental Cooperation, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - History and National Identity Colloquium, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Role of ENGOs in North America, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Reinventing North America, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Transboundary Resource Inventory Project, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Prospects for a North American Free Trade Agreement papers, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Energy and Environment, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Harnessing Knowledge: Implementing the Agenda for North American Collaboration in Higher Education, Research and Training, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Winners and Losers Report, 1991 May 17-19 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Harmonizing Competitiveness Conference Papers, 1991 November 8-10 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - NAMI Meeting - Monterrey, Mexico, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Ottawa Forum, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Border Environmental Assembly (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Beyond Nafta, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NGOs in North America, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Record, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Stanford/NAMI (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Wirth Letters, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NAMI (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New Direction, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Palm Springs (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Japan's Relations with North America: The New Pacific Interface, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Videotapes
    - Libre Comercio v.c.1, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Libre Comercio v.c.2, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Libre Comercio v.c.3, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Libre Comercio v.c.4, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Libre Comercio v.c.5, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Libre Comercio v.c.6, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - North American Institute, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - The NBC Nightly News Report on the experience of an SCA Conservation Crew in the Rocky Mountain National Park, Saturday July 22, 2000, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Closing Plenary, Novermber 4, 1994, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - World Affairs Television-Capital Connection #1325, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - From Treaty to Trust, 1995-1998, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Columbia Treaty History, January 1998, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - The Heritage Minutes – Complete Collection, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - The Great Canadian Quiz, Proud and Free, 1995, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Saving Their Corner of the Planet: Local Conservationists in Honduras, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - The Future of Work, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Sustainable Futures, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - National Press Club NAFTA debate, 10/22/1993, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - MacNeils/Lehrer News Hour (NAFTA Segment Featuring San Luis Potosi, Mexico), 11/11/1993, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
    - Danzante, 07/02/1992, videotape (VHS) (Box 18)
  - Audio tapes
    - Goals and Mission #1, 6/4/1989, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Goals and Mission #2, 6/4/1989, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Canada Session 6/3/1989, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - United States Session, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Johns Wirth (Fri Nite), audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Tape #1, 3/31/2001, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Tape #2, 3/31/2001, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Tape #3, 3/31/2001, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Tape #4, 3/31/2001, audiocassette (Box 18)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #1, Part 1, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #1, Part 2, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #2, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #3, Part 1, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #3, Part 2, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #4, Part 1, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #4, Part 2, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #5, Part 1, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #5, Part 2, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Monterrey Mexico- #6, 1990 May; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - All Things Considered, 1988 April 1; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Santa Fe-Tape 1, 1991 November 9; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Santa Fe-Tape 2, 1991 November 9; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Santa Fe-Tape 3, 1991 November 9; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Santa Fe-Tape 4, 1991 November 9; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Santa Fe-Tape 5, 1991 November 9; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Santa Fe-Tape 6, 1991 November 9; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Session I/Session II, 1/25/1997, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Media Colloquium-#1, 1994 March 11-13; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Media Colloquium-#2, 1994 March 11-13; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Media Colloquium-#3, 1994 March 11-13; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - NAFTA/Media-Summary & Conclusion, 1994 March 13, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Media Conference, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - NAMI Planning Mtg #1, 1994 October 22; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - NAMI Planning Mtg #2, 1994 October 22; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - NAMI Planning Mtg #4, 1994 October 22; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Comm. Service & Volunteering-Tape 1, 1999 September 24-26; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Comm. Service & Volunteering-Tape 2, 1999 September 24-26; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Comm. Service & Volunteering-Tape 3, 1999 September 24-26; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Comm. Service & Volunteering-Tape 4, 1999 September 24-26; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Martin Vs. Quintana, 2004 July 22, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Media Conference, Bill Roberts Keynote, 2000, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Cultural Landscapes and Historic Communities: Mexican Perspectives, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North American Institute-1, 1994 May 7; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North American Institute-1, 1994 May 7; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North American Institute-2, 1994 May 7; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North American Institute-3, 1994 May 7; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North American Institute-4, 1994 May 7; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North American Institute-3, May 8, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - [unlabeled], audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Session 1, 35455; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Session 2, 35455; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Session 3, 35456; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Session 3, 35456; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - North America Institute, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 1-Trade Corridors, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 2-Trade Corridors, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 3-Trade Corridors, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 4-Trade Corridors, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 4-Trade Corridors, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Env. Colloquium #1, 2/1993, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Env. Colloquium #2, 2/1993, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Env. Colloquium #2.5, 2/1993, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Env. Colloquium #6, 2/1993, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - 2A-Sat a.m. - more discussion/2B, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - 3A/3B, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #1, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #2, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #3, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #4, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #5, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #6, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #7, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ENGO #8, 2/10 – 12/95; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Traduccion – 1, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Traduccion – 2, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Traduccion – 3, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Traduccion – 4, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - 1, June 22 1998; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - 2, June 22 1998; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - 3, June 22 1998; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 1, 36026; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 2, 36026; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 3, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 4, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 5, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 6, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 7, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 8, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Tape 9, 36027; audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Closing Lunch, 8/20/1998, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Chretien/Wirth Interview, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Amb. Chretien Luncheon, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Montreal-1&2, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Montreal-Tape 2, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - Montreal-3, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ID Conference-Tape #1, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ID Conference-Tape #4, audiocassette (Box 19)
    - ID Conference-Tape #, audiocassette (Box 19)